♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely?
♪ Lucky there's a family guy
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us
♪ Laugh and cry
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
♪ Everyone has fingernails
♪ And everyone wants cash
♪ So send us all
your fingernails ♪
♪ And we'll send you
some cash ♪
♪ Fingernails for cash
dot com ♪
♪ Remember it's just
fingernails ♪
♪ So don't expect much cash
♪ Fingernails for cash dot com
♪ Our service never fails
♪ Just take the cash
♪ And don't ask why
♪ We want your fingernails
♪ 'Cause we might be building
a fort with them. ♪
Here you go, fellas.
Thanks, Horace.
Oh, here, let me
get this one, Peter.
Geez, what the hell kind of
stupid wallet is that, Joe?
(sighs) Bonnie's
making wallets now.
Look, she's gonna ask
you guys to buy one.
I'll just give
you the money.
Just don't throw it out
within five miles
of where we live.
Hey, why do you have a
Harvard dining hall I.D.?
I pulled over some
punk Harvard kid
who gave me a bunch of
lip, so I took his I.D.
Man, I bet they got fancy food
up there at Harvard.
Like them turkeys
with paper shoes.
Or pigs with apples
in their mouths.
Or them lambs what ain't never
seen the light before.
Oh, yeah, I love
eating food that's sad.
Hey, you know,
we should drive up there
and use that card
to eat for free.
That's a
great idea!
Let's go
to Harvard!
Oh, I don't know, you guys.
We'll be as out of place there
as a black guy in Sweden.
CROWD:
Ooh!
Blackin sippin.
Ya, blackin
sippin.
♪
Wow, so this
is it.
Harvard
University.
The alma mater
of Fred Grandy,
Amy Brenneman
and Ted Kaczynski.
Are we sure this is
the way to the dining hall?
Oh, I'm sorry, are your feet
getting tired?
God, I'd love to be able to
wheel around in a toy all day.
Ah, this is
it, you guys.
The Harvard
Dining Hall.
Holy crap!
This place
is amazing!
And just think, this is
where Helen Keller
used to eat
when she went here.
Tonight, I want to go out
and just get wasted.
And not one
of these campus bars.
I want to get wrecked
by a townie.
Helen, you're
outrageous.
I can't believe you're
getting away with this.
I've been getting away
with this since I was seven.
Believe me, I know
what I'm doing.
Good morning, girls.
Helen.
(moaning)
No freaking way.
They have breakfast for dinner.
Lois never lets me do that!
(line ringing)
Lois, do you have any idea
what I'm looking at right now?
LOIS: Peter, we're not
doing this again.
I am at Harvard,
the smartest school in
the country, and they have...
Peter, breakfast
for dinner is anarchy.
It's fun, Lois!
It's whimsical!
It's ridiculous!
Pancakes are not
a nighttime food.
You're ridiculous!
Boy, breakfast
for dinner is
a real hot-button issue
for you guys, huh?
She's also mad
'cause I shook Stewie
and now he's
walking weird.
Hey, was Beowulf
a Teen Wolf sequel
with Scott Baio?
No.
(sighs) Then I just
totally failed
that Medieval Lit
midterm.
So this is
a Harvard bar, huh?
Seems pretty normal.
Hey, check it out,
there's the
Winklevoss twins.
Let's get a drink.
Get a drink.
I thought of it first.
Hey, you guys noticed
how many Asians
there are at
this school?
I mean, how'd they
all get so smart?
I don't know. Guess that's just
the way God made 'em.
Gentlemen, I give you...
the Asian.
Ooh...
Compact, hairless
and fiercely intelligent.
The penises, while tiny,
are extremely efficient.
We're projecting ten billion
within five years.
Also, there'll be
different varieties
that will all hate each other
for some reason.
Do they eat just,
like, regular food?
(chuckling):
No, no, no, the opposite.
♪
All right, this
is more like it.
Way better than that
lame-ass college joint.
Yeah, finally
a terrible Boston bar
with a giant low-def TV.
Let's go, Celtics!
I think that's
The Dr. Oz Show.
What are you talking about?
This is the last scene
of Independence Day.
Hey, look, even
the bartender's low-def.
Hey, what can I
get you fellas?
Hey, what do you say
we get some shots?
Yeah! Let's
get wasted!
Yeah! Let's get
wicked bombed!
Sorry, pal, we already have
an intense wheelchair guy.
Well, now,
hold on, hold on.
What's your name, friend?
Peter.
Yeah, we already got
a wheelchair guy.
♪
Oh, hey, Stewie.
Hey, sometimes when
daddies drive home drunk,
they come from
far away places,
but it's okay because
they didn't get arrested
and they're still
kind of drunk
so they-they think
it's okay.
You should know that Mom
has emotionally let you go.
It won't be long
before she takes a lover.
Ah, my head!
She already has
two cell phones.
Aw, man, what happened
last night?
WOMAN (gruff voice):
I can tell you what happened.
What the...?
Who the hell are you?
Who the hell do you
think I am, sweetie?
Oh, no. You mean...?
That's right, baby.
As of last night,
we're man and wife.
By the way, I need
you to call my pimp
and tell him I quit.
Oh, my God, I...
I married a hooker?
Married?
All right,
bachelor party!
Come on!
Back to Boston!
Aw, aw, damn it.
I guess we're not going.
Hey, Stewie,
here's five bucks.
Get naked.
This... this can't be possible!
I can't be married
to a prostitute!
Where will you two be going
on your scummymoon?
And can I plan your
bridal golden shower?
I don't even know your name!
It's Charmese.
Perfect.
Listen, Charmese, I was
obviously very, very drunk.
This whole thing
is a huge mistake.
Now, we got to
fix this right away.
Like hell we do,
sweet cream.
This is just what
I've always wanted:
to settle down,
find a husband
and live the
married life.
And now I got that.
Your new wife
is a human toilet.
Look, I don't remember
anything about last night.
How do I... how do I even know
we're really married?
I got our marriage certificate
right here.
It's legit.
And it looks like I signed
one of the witness lines
and Peter partially signed
the other.
(chuckles)
Joe, look.
You know, after 40 years
in my line of work,
I've learned the difference
between true love
and doing the entire bowling
team of a pizza restaurant
on a box spring by a brook.
This is true love.
Hey, what's our
last name again?
You know, Quagmire,
I was thinking last night,
I might remember Charmese
from a stag party in 1991.
Ask her if she remembers
getting hit in the forehead
with a meatball sandwich.
You guys, I can't
stay married to her.
This whole thing
is a complete disaster!
In fact, you know what?
I got to go down
to the courthouse right now
and file for divorce.
This thing ends now.
Hang on,
Quagmire.
I'm not sure
that's a good idea.
Quahog has some extremely
draconian laws governing divorce
that all heavily
favor the woman.
What? What do you mean?
Well, to be honest,
if you divorce her,
she'll probably get
everything you have.
What? No,
that's impossible!
I can't lose all
my money and my house!
Then I'll have
to move into some
depressing divorced
guy apartment!
As you can see,
we have plenty
of cabinet space
for your plate.
The oven, of course,
is just decorative.
Seems okay.
Do you have any other
units available?
This is our only one.
MAN (screaming):
I hope you're happy, Marsha!
(thud) We might have
something upstairs.
Sorry, Quagmire,
but the only way
around the law
is if the woman
consents to a divorce.
Consent?
But Charmese will
never agree to that.
You heard her, the crazy skank
wants to be a wife.
She's found
herself a husband
and she's not
letting go.
I bet she's what happens
if you put a Hooters girl
in the microwave on "high."
Well, the only
other choice
is to let her take
all your money.
(sighs) Well, I
obviously can't do that.
I guess I'm just gonna
have to suck it up...
Let her suck it up-- she's
the expert. Sorry, keep going.
...and at least try to make
things work with Charmese.
And who knows?
Maybe it... maybe it
won't be that bad.
After all, I liked her enough
to marry her last night.
I must've seen
something in her.
There you go, that's
the spirit, buddy.
There's a little bit
of good in everyone.
Except that president guy
from The Hunger Games.
He was pretty bad.
This year, in addition
to the Hunger Games,
we're going to do
the Special Hunger Games.
I'm Andy!
I love
you, Andy!
Come on,
guys, fight.
So, Doc, I figured
if Charmese and I
are gonna live
as man and wife,
I ought to get
her checked out.
Of course. Charmese,
when's the last time
you had a pelvic exam?
When was
the Missouri Compromise?
Uh, I think 1821.
Then I've never
had a pelvic exam.
All right,
I'm going in.
If I tug on the rope twice,
that means pull me out.
(squishy footsteps)
HARTMAN:
God, who are the pigs
who just throw their
empty beer cans down here?
Hey, Charmese.
You know, I really
love your clothes...
I found a lot of them
on strung-out
teenage corpses.
That's so lovely.
But I was thinking,
maybe this afternoon
you'd like to borrow
my credit card
and buy yourself
a new wardrobe.
You know, something
a little more conservative.
Really?
That's so
sweet, Glenn.
No one's ever cared
about me like that before.
Thank you.
♪ Uptown girl
♪ She's been living
in her uptown world ♪
♪ I bet she never had
a backstreet guy ♪
♪ I bet her mama
never told her why ♪
♪ I'm gonna try
for an uptown girl ♪
♪ She's been living
in her white bread world ♪
♪ As long as anyone
with hot blood can... ♪
I would like to pawn
all these clothes
for crack money.
Gosh, thanks so much
for having us over, you guys.
Of course, Glenn.
Welcome to our
home, Charmese.
Sit anywhere you like.
That chair with the garbage bag
taped over it looks pretty good.
Meg, you look
pretty next to her.
So, Charmese,
I was thinking
of writing an article
about you
for my school paper.
Do you charge black guys
more or less?
Hmm, that's a hard question
to answer.
Most of them get a group rate.
Come on, now,
let's not talk about work.
It's a dinner party.
Are you and Glenn
thinking about children?
Unfortunately,
I can't have children.
Oh, menopause?
No, I got knifed
in the vagina one Christmas.
Ah, the holidays
are always stressful.
I have $3.74.
Do something to me.
(hawks, spits)
I love you.
I want to take you
away from all this.
They're supposedly putting
an ice cream place
where the shoe store was.
Excuse me, Lois,
where's your bathroom?
I got to check on
a whistling sound.
Upstairs, to the left.
Um, I'm obsessed
with Charmese.
Hey.
Let's do it.
What? You mean, like sex?
Yeah, and we
should go now.
I just stuffed everything
back into place.
Uh, you know, Charmese,
I don't really think
I'm in the mood.
What? You're never
in the mood.
We've been married
two weeks,
and we haven't done it
since that first night.
I haven't gone two
weeks without sex
since I was in a
coma for six weeks.
Yeah, sorry, Charmese,
I'm-I'm just not feeling it.
Geez, what the hell's
your problem?
What are... what are you,
gay or something?
Excuse me?
You heard me.
Are you some kind of 'mo?
Oh, God, please tell me I'm
not married to some Nancy boy.
Why? Would that
be a problem?
Are you kidding?
Course it would.
My dream is to live the
married life and settle down.
I can't be doing
that with no gay.
I see.
Well, Charmese,
I have something to tell you,
and this isn't easy.
But I'm gay.
What? No.
You can't be.
I was gonna be your
perfect little wife.
I was gonna make you
breakfast maybe once a week,
and give you stuff to do
right when you walk through
the door after work.
And I would've
loved that, Charmese,
if I just weren't
so super duper double gay.
(sobbing):
Oh, this is awful.
Aw, don't cry, Charmese.
You'll find the right guy.
There's someone
for everyone.
Even if you're
a narcissistic pedophile.
Hey, Ma, we got any pictures
of me when I was a kid?
Maybe something in a tub?
I'm really sorry it
didn't work out, Glenn.
Me, too, Charmese.
I'll send
the divorce papers
to that Rite Aid
where you brush your teeth.
Hey, buddy, what happened?
She gone?
Yep, I'm off
the hook, Peter.
I told Charmese
I was gay,
and now she's gonna consent
to a no-fault divorce.
That's brilliant,
Quagmire.
It's the exact opposite
of what Hugh Jackman does.
Pretend you're gay
to get out of marriage.
(sighs)
Thank God.
I really dodged
a bullet there.
I don't know what the
hell I was thinking.
Eh, everybody
makes mistakes.
Even doctors.
(prolonged beep)
You forgot to say...
I forgot to say "clear."
(sighs)
Finally, back to my old life.
Hello, Internet porn.
Man, I haven't done this
in two weeks.
I should weigh myself
before and after.
Sorry, I forgot
my prescription mouthwash.
Aah!
Oh, my God.
What are you watching?
That... that's
straight porn.
Listen, Charmese, it's not
what you think, all right?
I've been poisoned,
and I'm trying to
make myself throw up.
Gay men don't watch
straight porn.
You lied to me,
you son of a bitch.
No, no, I'm gay, I swear!
Here, watch me,
uh, uh, go there.
Jen Aniston?
More like Jen
Can't-get-a-man-iston!
See? I went there.
Damn it, Glenn,
if you're not gay,
then the divorce is off.
No, no, I am.
I swear to God.
All right, fine.
If you're really gay
and you want that divorce,
all you got to do is one thing.
Anything, Charmese. Name it.
Prove it.
Let me watch you have sex
with a man.
Wh-What?
You heard me.
I want to see you
get it on with a guy.
(sighs)
All right, Charmese,
I'll do it.
If that's what it takes,
I'll have sex with another man.
(bell rings)
Look, Daddy.
Teacher says every
time a bell rings,
some gay guy's gonna have
sex with another gay guy.
We're gonna pull you
out of that school.
TV ANNOUNCER: We now return to
The Dyslexic Baseball Wrap-Up.
And the Yew Nork Nankees
bave heaten
the Oltimore Borioles nive
to foo here at Yamden Cards.
The Borioles now
lace a fong toad rip
where they'll
face the Sed Rox,
the Revil Days
and the Jue Blays.
(knocking)
Hey, Peter, you got a minute?
Oh, yeah, sure.
Come on in, Quagmire.
Listen, um, I need
to ask you to do something,
and it's something huge.
I mean, it's, like,
the biggest thing
a guy could ever ask
his friend to do.
Hey, we're best pals, right?
Whatever you need.
All right,
and you have to understand,
I would never ask you to do this
if I had any other choice
and if what were at stake
was anything less
than my entire way of life.
Geez, Quagmire, what is it?
Charmese won't
give me a divorce
because she doesn't
believe I'm gay,
so I need you to have sex
with me while she watches.
I have some demands.
Of course, of course.
Nobody can ever know.
Absolutely. I'm right there
with you on that one.
There will be no
kissing on the mouth.
Okay.
I changed my mind.
There will be kissing
on the mouth.
Uh, all right.
Good. Now, what else?
What else? Uh, yes.
If, per chance,
it is beautiful,
I reserve the
right to cry.
Peter, I can't imagine
any scenario
where this
is gonna be beautiful.
Oh, I can.
I'm a very
passionate man.
Haven't you ever seen
my Spanish soap operas?
Mi amor!
Papa!
Ni├▒o!
Bueno.
Peter, can we just
get out of here?
I want to get
this over with.
This was part
of the deal, Quagmire.
I need this
to be a lovely evening.
Fine.
How was work today?
I don't want to talk
about work.
Hey, should we go
someplace else for dessert?
You know, someplace fun,
downtown,
where the college kids go?
What? I'm not taking you to
two different restaurants.
Huh. Hard to believe
your marriage isn't working out.
A rose for the gentleman?
What? No. Scram.
Hey, I'm not just
a poorly cleaned butt.
There's a whole man around it
you have to please.
Fine.
Here.
Quagmire, what's going on
with you?
You don't seem
very present tonight.
Why are you so tense?
I'm tense because I have
to bang you in 20 minutes!
Well, if it's so much
of a chore.
What the (bleep) is
going on with my life?
Okay, Charmese, here we go.
Are you sure you want
to watch this?
I'm just warning you,
you're in the splash zone.
Ugh, if I get anything
out, I'll be happy.
Get on with it.
Uh, okay.
Here, let me
stroke your hair.
Thank you.
I want to do gay
things for you.
I... I crave your groin.
Yes, and I cannot wait
to intertwine our bodies
and make each other's
fingers smell terrible.
Enough! Kiss each other.
(vomiting)
(gulps)
Oh, yeah,
that was so hot.
Just like we always do.
Now take off
each other's clothes.
(sobbing): Oh, God, I'm so
excited for gay sex.
(crying):
Me, too.
Your body makes me
so horny.
Shut up and do it.
(whimpering)
It's very close, Peter.
The paintbrush
is about to touch the canvas.
Come on, Peter.
Sir Ian McKellen does this.
You can do this.
Here we go.
Here we go!
Just do it!
Wait.
(sighs)
Stop.
Look, Glenn,
you're obviously not gay.
Ye I am.
Well, I'm something
'cause I've been at full-sail
for the last half hour.
No, Glenn, you're not.
I see that now,
and the truth is,
if you're willing to go
this far to get a divorce,
then maybe we shouldn't
be married after all.
What... what are you saying?
I'm saying,
I'll give you your divorce.
You're off the hook.
Oh.
Oh, thank you, Charmese.
Thank you so much.
I-I can't believe
you'd do that for me.
Well, it's for me, too.
You were real nice
to me, Glenn,
nicer than
any other guy's been,
but I wanted
to be somebody's wife,
not somebody's burden.
Good luck to you, sweetie.
And good luck to
you, Charmese.
Thanks.
You're very special to me.
I'm sorry my urine melted a hole
through your toilet.
Aw.
(sighs)
Thank God that's over.
Yeah, no kidding.
Hey, you know, there's not
too many guys in the world
who would be willing to do
something like that
for their pal.
Ah, don't mention it.
No, no,
you're an amazing friend,
and I really owe you.
Thanks, Peter.
Ah, you're welcome, buddy.
Hey, Quagmire, why is the red
light blinking on your computer?
STEWIE: What are
we watching? Glee?
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru